Mei, do you want to join us?
Mei, chciałabyś do nas dołączyć?
Join you?
„Dołączyć”?
Right. Let's purify this dirty world together.
Tak, razem oczyśćmy ten brudny świat.
Miho, do you want to let her in Perfect?
Miho, chcesz ją dopuścić do Idealnej?
Hello?
Halo?
Today?
Dzisiaj?
Sure, no problem.
Jasne, nie ma sprawy.
Okay, take care of this.
Dobra, zajmij się tym.
Where do you want to meet?
Gdzie się spotykamy?
I wish I had a boyfriend.
Też chciałabym mieć chłopaka.
I know. I heard he's a medical intern.
Wiadomo. Podobno jest stażystą w szpitalu.
Seriously?
Naprawdę?
At her dad's hospital.
W szpitalu jej ojca.
Awesome.
Super.
"Perfect Justice."
„Idealna sprawiedliwość”.
The other members just call it "Perfect."
Inne członkinie nazywają ją „Idealna”.
Members?
Członkinie?
The people who know the account ID and password.
Osoby mające login i hasło.
We all use and post from the same account.
Wszystkie używamy tego samego konta.
You can never tell anyone else the password.
Nie wolno zdradzać innym hasła.
Okay.
Dobrze.
Only people that Miho chooses can learn the password.
Miho decyduje, kto poznaje hasło.
You have to promise.
Musisz obiecać.
So, what should I do?
Co mam zrobić?
If you fight against something that you don't like,
Jeśli coś ci się nie podoba,
post a photo or video of it here.
zamieść zdjęcie albo filmik, jak z tym walczysz.
Really?
Naprawdę?
Mao, it sounds like we're doing evil when you talk like that.
Mao, to brzmi tak, jakbyśmy robiły coś złego.
Oh, right. Perfect is for doing justice.
Chodzi o wymierzanie sprawiedliwości.
-Justice? -Right.
- Co? - Właśnie.
We fix what's wrong with the world,
Naprawiamy świat
and our movement will spread around the world.
i mamy nadzieję, że nasz ruch się rozrośnie.
For example,
Na przykład...
this.
to.
I posted this yesterday.
Wrzuciłam to wczoraj.
No, no!
Nie!
Really? Is that so?
Naprawdę?
-You did that, Sarina? -I hate when people walk while smoking.
- To ty, Sarina? - Nienawidzę ludzi palących na ulicy.
Here's what I did.
Ja zrobiłam to.
On TV, I saw it's dangerous to park bicycles on tactile paving.
Widziałam w telewizji, że parkowanie rowerów na chodniku jest niebezpieczne.
Nice work, Mao!
Dobra robota, Mao.
That's cool, but what if people find out we're doing it?
Podoba mi się to, ale co, jeśli ludzie się o tym dowiedzą?
Don't worry. We'll never tell anyone who the other members are.
Nie martw się, nigdy nie powiemy nikomu, kim są pozostałe członkinie.
We also don't ask who posted what. It's our rule.
Nie pytamy, kto co udostępnił. Takie są zasady.
I see.
Rozumiem.
Even if there's trouble, we have Miho's dad.
A w razie problemów mamy tatę Miho.
You post stuff too, Mei, and purify this dirty world!
Działaj z nami, Mei. Oczyszczajmy razem świat!
-Okay? -You're so enthusiastic, Sarina.
- Dobrze? - Co za entuzjazm, Sarina.
-I was just imitating Miho. -That's not like her at all.
- Udaję Miho. - Ona wcale tak nie mówi.
EPISODE 4
ODCINEK 4
-What?
- Co?
What is it?
Co to?
-We've got signal? -"Perfect Justice has tweeted"?
Mamy zasięg?
I got the same message.
Dostałam tę samą wiadomość.
Me too.
Ja też.
Forget that! Call the police!
Nieważne! Dzwońcie na policję!
Let's see, 119.
Dobrze, 119.
Dummy! It's 110!
To 110, idiotko!
CANNOT CONNECT NO SIGNAL
BRAK ZASIĘGU
Damn it!
Cholera!
It's Wi-Fi! We don't have signal, but we've got Wi-Fi.
To Wi-Fi! Nie mamy zasięgu, tylko Wi-Fi.
It's so darn slow!
Jest takie wolne!
Ayaka, text someone.
Napisz do kogoś, Ayaka.
To whom?
Do kogo?
Anyone! Just call for help!
Nieważne! Proś o pomoc!
Help...
Pomocy...
No way.
O nie.
-The Wi-Fi is down. -What about you?
- Wi-Fi już nie działa. - A u ciebie?
Why didn't you text faster, Ayaka?
Mogłaś pisać szybciej, Ayaka!
Shut up, Mana!
Zamknij się, Mana!
-You tried to call an ambulance. -Shut up!
- Ty wybrałaś numer pogotowia. - Cicho!
-Shut yourself up! -Hey!
- Zamknij się! - Hej!
-What? -Perfect's message.
- Co? - Ten tweet.
-Look! -What?
- Patrz! - Co?
What is this?
Co to jest?
Wow, you're right.
Faktycznie.
It's that message again.
To znowu ta wiadomość.
The only people who know this account's ID and password...
Wszystkie, które znają login i hasło...
Are just us here and Miho.
Są tutaj. No, poza Miho.
So, Miho posted this?
Miho to wrzuciła?
But there's also this possibility.
Jest jeszcze jedna możliwość.
It could be a message from Sarina and the others that disappeared.
Może to wiadomość od Sariny albo innych, które zniknęły.
They're alive?
One żyją?
They may have gotten away, and they are telling us something.
Może udało im się uciec i chcą nam coś przekazać.
I doubt that.
Wątpię.
Why?
Dlaczego?
Look at the time it was posted.
Spójrz na godzinę opublikowania.
At exactly 12 o'clock.
Dokładnie o północy.
We were all here then, except Miho.
Byłyśmy tu wszystkie poza Miho.
Right.
Faktycznie.
Also, we haven't had signal here the whole time.
I nie miałyśmy zasięgu.
Then it's definitely Miho.
Czyli to Miho.
Miho again?
Znowu Miho?
Since this photo and message keep showing up,
Skoro ciągle widzimy to zdjęcie i wiadomość,
she definitely wants us to remember something.
pewnie chce, żebyśmy sobie coś przypomniały.
But why would Miho do anything so annoyingly complex?
Dlaczego Miho robi coś tak irytująco skomplikowanego?
-Isn't it obvious? -What?
- Czy to nie oczywiste? - Co?
I mean, you were the first ones to ignore Miho.
Wy pierwsze zignorowałyście Miho.
It wasn't me. It was Mana.
To nie ja, tylko Mana.
Don't blame me!
Nie obwiniaj mnie!
You were happiest to hear the news about Miho's dad.
Ucieszyła cię wiadomość o ojcu Miho.
-I've got it! -Got what?
- Wiem! - Co?
Twelve o'clock!
Chodzi o godzinę!
-We have to do something fast! -Do what?
- Musimy się pospieszyć! - Ale z czym?
This post made me realize that it's exactly at 12 o'clock
Zorientowałam się, że dokładnie o 12
when the lights go out and someone disappears.
gasną światła i ktoś znika.
What do you mean?
Co masz na myśli?
How long ago did Sarina disappear?
Kiedy zniknęła Sarina?
I think...
Chyba...
it was 20 minutes ago.
z 20 minut temu.
Twenty minutes.
Dwadzieścia minut.
There!
Tam!
Mei disappeared about...
Mei zniknęła...
thirty minutes ago.
jakieś 30 minut temu.
I don't understand.
Nie rozumiem.
When a clock in this room gets to 12 o'clock,
Kiedy któryś z zegarów wybija 12,
the lights go out.
wyłączają się światła.
No way! When's the next time?
Co? Kiedy znowu się to stanie?
Isn't it just coincidence?
Może to zwykły przypadek?
You're right.
Masz rację.
There's no proof it was at 12 o'clock.
Nie mamy dowodu, że chodzi o 12.
There is a total of...
Tutaj jest...
twelve clocks.
dwanaście zegarów.
Twelve clocks.
Dwanaście zegarów.
Twelve chairs.
Dwanaście krzeseł.
There were 12 members in Perfect, right?
Dwanaście członkiń Idealnej.
We'll be vanished at 12 o'clock!
Znikniemy o 12!
When will it be 12 o'clock again?
Kiedy znowu wybije 12?
-That one! -Oh, no!
- Tam! - O nie!
What should we do to save us?
Jak mamy się uratować?
We have to remember something!
Musimy sobie coś przypomnieć!
But what is it?
Ale co?
If she's posting on here,
Skoro publikuje tutaj,
then maybe we're supposed to remember something
może chodzi o coś
about posts on Justice.
związanego ze Sprawiedliwością.
Repent what we did?
Mamy odpokutować?
Repent? Miho encouraged us to do it.
Ale za co? To był pomysł Miho.
You're right.
Racja.
She was always all righteous and like, "Let's purify this dirty world!"
Zawsze była taka prawa i chciała naprawiać świat.
Ultimately, we practically committed minor crimes.
W efekcie popełniałyśmy drobne wykroczenia.
Not "practically." That was totally wrong.
To prawda. To było złe.
Don't act like you didn't, too!
Też to robiłaś!
But Miho forced us to do that stuff.
Ale Miho nas zmusiła.
Get back on track! We're almost out of time!
Uspokójcie się! Czas nam się kończy.
What is it, Shiho?
O co chodzi, Shiho?
A victim of Perfect.
Ofiara Idealnej.
It might be a victim of Perfect.
Może chodzić o ofiarę Idealnej.
Come to think of it, that makes sense.
Właściwie to ma sens.
I can't understand.
Nie rozumiem.
If victims of Perfect got together and wanted revenge on us,
Gdyby ofiary Idealnej zebrały się i chciały na nas zemścić,
they would first go after...
zaczęłyby od...
Miho, right?
Miho, prawda?
She's the leader of Perfect.
Ona była liderką.
You mean, they got the password from Miho
Może wzięli od niej hasło
and made this post?
i dodali tego posta?
And they're going to lock us away somewhere?
I zamknęli nas tutaj?
If that's true, it all adds up.
Wtedy wszystko miałoby sens.
From Miho's disappearance to everything else.
Począwszy od zniknięcia Miho po wszystko inne.
Let's hurry up and confess everything we did on Perfect!
Szybko! Wyznajmy wszystko, co zamieściłyśmy na Idealnej.
CANNOT RETRIEVE USER DATA. TRY LATER.
NIE MOŻNA POBRAĆ DANYCH
-Kage, give me your phone. -What?
- Kage, daj mi telefon. - Co?
You had Twitter open. I can't read it on mine.
Miałaś otwartego Twittera, nie mogę nic odczytać u siebie.
Who did this?
Kto to zrobił?
Who vandalized the car of the guy who ran that sweatshop?
Kto zniszczył samochód właściciela sklepu?
You don't want a guy like that as an enemy.
Nie chcemy mieć kogoś takiego za wroga.
When was that posted?
Jaka jest data posta?
July 20.
Dwudziesty lipca.
I knew it. That was Sarina and Mei.
Wiedziałam. To Sarina i Mei.
Look.
Patrz.
No, a little left.
Nie, w lewo.
-Left? -Right there.
- W lewo? - Tam.
A little farther back.
Kawałek do tyłu.
No, I mean forward.
Nie, do przodu.
Sorry.
Przepraszam.
A little more...
Jeszcze kawałek...
Here. Look at this.
Hej, spójrzcie na to.
You're right.
Masz rację.
So, they were vanished because of that?
Zniknęły przez to?
Somebody, do something!
Niech ktoś coś zrobi!
I'll confess! Give it to me!
Ja się przyznam! Daj mi to!
I did this.
Zrobiłam to.
I compiled the writing mistakes of Mr. Fujiwara, the literature teacher,
Zebrałam błędy pana Fujiwary, nauczyciela literatury,
and posted them.
i je udostępniłam.
-That's when Perfect was doing good! -We're out of time!
- To było coś dobrego! - Kończy nam się czas!
What?
Co?
We're all here.
Wszystkie tu jesteśmy.
-Thank goodness. -We can't relax yet.
- Dzięki Bogu. - To jeszcze nie koniec.
Doesn't it mean we're wrong about our kidnapper being a victim of Perfect?
Chyba się pomyliłyśmy i porywacz nie jest ofiarą Idealnej.
Then, who do you think it is?
To kim jest?
Well, it must be...
Myślę, że to...
What?
Co?
Doesn't that sound like...
Czy to nie brzmi jak...
Is it Miho?
To Miho?
Excuse me...
Przepraszam...
Who are you?
Kim jesteś?
Don't do it, Kyoko!
Kyoko, nie rób tego!
Wait!
Zaczekaj!
Can you please tell us...
Powiedz nam...
what we have to do to be released?
co mamy zrobić, żeby się uwolnić?
Why did you do that, Kyoko?
Kyoko, czemu to zrobiłaś?
Don't talk too loud.
Nie mów tak głośno.
-They might be listening? -Who was that?
- Mogą nas podsłuchiwać. - Kto to był?
I don't know.
Nie wiem.
A victim of Perfect?
Ofiara Idealnej?
The owner of that sweatshop?
Właściciel sklepu?
For that little thing?
Za coś takiego?
His clothes and shoes looked expensive.
Miał drogie ubrania i buty.
With that limp,
Kulał,
I could have taken him down.
mogłam go załatwić.
Don't say that.
Nie mów tak.
Isn't it strange he would be working with that limp?
Czy to nie dziwne, że pracuje mimo problemu z nogą?
I thought so, too.
Właśnie.
And that bag
A ten worek...
was the same one we had on our heads.
Miałyśmy na głowach takie same.
-So, he's the same as us. -The same?
- Jest taki jak my. - Co?
He may have been kidnapped too.
Może jego też porwano.
Then, he might help us?
Może mógłby nam pomóc?
I know!
Wiem!
That supermarket manager we denounced
Menadżer supermarketu, na którego doniosłyśmy,
had a bad leg, too.
też miał problem z nogą.
He did?
Tak?
Yes, I'm sure.
Na pewno.
This must mean they want us to confess to our crimes.
Czyli chcą, żebyśmy się przyznały do naszych przestępstw.
I just said everything I did.
Ja już wszystko powiedziałam.
That clock is...
Zegar zaraz...
about to strike 12 o'clock. Somebody say something!
wybije 12. Niech któraś się przyzna.
But nothing happened earlier.
Ale ostatnio nic się nie stało.
But since nobody disappeared last time,
No właśnie, dlatego teraz
two might go this time.
mogą zniknąć dwie z nas.
Give me your phone, Kage.
Kage, daj mi swój telefon.
I think we need to talk about what we did as Perfect.
Chyba wszystkie musimy wyznać, co zrobiłyśmy w ramach Idealnej.
What about this?
Co z tym?
We shoplifted meat that had the expiration dates falsified
Ukradłyśmy mięso, które miało sfałszowaną datę ważności,
and threw it away.
i wyrzuciłyśmy je.
Who did this?
Która to zrobiła?
Are you going to ask about everything?
Będziesz pytać o wszystko?
So...
Czyli...
you want to stay here?
wolisz tu zostać?
I don't!
Nie!
I mean, today is graduation day.
Dzisiaj ostatni dzień szkoły.
Then you start!
To zacznij od siebie!
Don't shout.
Nie krzycz.
Excuse me.
Przepraszam.
You're here because you were kidnapped too, right?
Ciebie też porwano, prawda?
Please help us!
Pomóż nam!
-Let's escape together! -Mana!
- Ucieknijmy razem! - Mana!
Please, help us? How do we unlock our feet?
Proszę, pomóż nam. Jak możemy uwolnić stopy?
What?
Co?
This.
To.
Who did it?
Kto to zrobił?
Probably Mao.
Pewnie Mao.
Do you have proof?
Masz dowód?
No, but she loves meat.
Nie, ale ona kocha mięso.
I'm sorry.
Przepraszam.
I remember Mao once said
Pamiętam, jak Mao mówiła,
her cousin works at that store.
że jej kuzyn pracuje w tym sklepie.
I knew it! Manager, it was Mao.
Wiedziałam! Menadżerze, to Mao!
So, please let us go!
Proszę, wypuść nas!
So, he's not that manager?
Czyli to jednak nie on?
PERFECT JUSTICE #PERVERT_TEACHER #FONDLER #PEDOPHILE #PERFECT
IDEALNA SPRAWIEDLIWOŚĆ #NAUCZYCIEL_ZBOCZENIEC #PEDOFIL
DONATION BOX
DATKI
and put all his cash in a donation box?
...i przekazała jego pieniądze na cele charytatywne?
Sorry.
Przepraszam.
I'm sorry.
Bardzo przepraszam.
What?
Co?
-He must be on our side. -Maybe.
- On musi być po naszej stronie. - Może.
He might help us if we talk to him.
Musimy z nim porozmawiać.
Release us all right now!
W tej chwili nas wypuść!
If you don't...
Jeśli nie...
Kage!
Kage!
God...
Boże...
Kage...
Kage...
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION.
PRZEDSTAWIONY SERIAL JEST FIKCJĄ.
Subtitle translation by Brian Athey
Napisy: Arianna Sugier